Guide to The University of Montana Department of Women's Studies Records 1971-2003
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
University of Montana Department of Women's Studies Records
1971-2003
University of Montana, Mansfield Library, Archives and Special Collections The University of Montana—Missoula Missoula, MT 59812 406-243-2053 http://www.lib.umt.edu/asc library.archives@umontana.edu
RG 087
University of Montana Department of Women's Studies
9.2 linear feet
The collection contains correspondence, notes, newsletters and committee information regarding the administration and development of the Women’s Studies program at The University of Montana-Missoula.
Historical Note
Women’s Studies is an interdisciplinary program at the University of Montana that first began development in the early 1970s. The first step in the development of Women’s Studies occurred in 1971 when eight faculty and community members collaborated to present a symposium on campus entitled, “Realities and Reaction: A Symposium on Women.” Following the symposium, faculty members began to offer courses focusing on women’s contributions to knowledge. Many of these courses were offered in collaboration with the Women’s Resource Center on campus.
In 1975, the first proposal for establishing a women’s studies concentration within the Liberal Arts major was presented to the faculty senate. Although the Senate approved the proposal, the program was not funded or implemented. The program continued to develop though the efforts of faculty on campus. In 1984 a brochure entitled “Women in Curriculum” was published. The brochure outlined over forty courses with an emphasis on women at the University of Montana. In September 1990, a final proposal to create a Women’s Studies emphasis within the department of Liberal Studies was submitted to the Board of Regents and accepted. The emphasis was implemented in the fall of 1991.
Fall of 1992 marked the first year of a significantly funded program with Professors Deborah Slicer and Bari Burke acting as co-directors. Fall of 1993 brought the authorization of a half-time director of Women’s Studies and Dr. Julia Watson served as director from 1993-1995. Since 1996, various directors and co-directors have developed and expanded the program. As of 2007, the Department offers a minor in Women and Gender Studies open to students of all majors, and a continually evolving course list.
This collection is comprised of the files of G.G. Weix, Women’s Studies program director from fall 1997-Spring 2001 and co-director of the program from fall 2001-spring 2003. The collection contains correspondence, notes, newsletters and committee information regarding the administration and development of the Women’s Studies program, correspondence and notes on committees and programs related to Women’s Studies, and information and newsletters about other women’s organizations both local and national. The collection includes course lists and curriculum information regarding classes offered through the program as well as courses cross-listed with other departments. The collection also includes notes, correspondence, and information regarding speakers and events organized by the department.
This collection is divided into 5 series:
Series I: Program Administration, 1987-2003, 2.2 linear feet
Series II: Related Committees and Programs, 1971-2003, 0.8 linear feet
Series III: Curriculum and Instruction, 1984-2003, 1.2 linear feet
Series IV: Speakers and Events, 1971-2003, 4.2 linear feet
Series V: Other Women's Organizations, 1991-2003, 0.8 linear feet
Researchers must use collection in accordance with the policies of Archives and Special Collections, the Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, and The University of Montana--Missoula.
Materials were held by G. G. Weix, Professor of Anthropology at The University of Montana, until their donation to the Archives.
Materials were donated to the Archives by G. G. Weix.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Women's studies--Montana--Missoula
Montana; Colleges and Universities; Women
- Program Administration, 1987-2003; Series I; 2.2 linear feet
  - Director's Correspondence, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Director's Correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Director Evaluation Correspondence, 2002 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Director's Notes, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Director's Notes, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Director: Position Description (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Director Search, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Director Search, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 1/8)
  - Director Search, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Director Search, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Director Search, 2001 (Box-folder 1/11)
  - Director Search, 2002 (Box-folder 1/12)
  - Program Coordinator Search, 2002 (Box-folder 1/13)
  - Faculty, 1984-1994 (Box-folder 2/1)
  - Faculty, 2001 (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Faculty Affiliates, 2000 (Box-folder 2/3)
  - Faculty Biographies, 1996 (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Faculty Correspondence, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 2/5)
  - Faculty Diversity Reports, 2002 (Box-folder 2/6)
  - Faculty Search, 1995 (Box-folder 2/7)
  - Faculty Search, 1996 (Box-folder 2/8)
  - Faculty Search, 2000 (Box-folder 2/9)
  - Faculty/Staff with International Qualifications, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 2/10)
  - Advisory Council, 1994 (Box-folder 3/1)
  - Evaluation Committees, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 3/2)
  - Long Term Planning Committee, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 3/3)
  - Steering Committee, 1991-2000 (Box-folder 3/4)
  - Steering Committee, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 3/5)
  - Steering Committee Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 3/6)
  - Steering Committee Memos, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 3/7)
  - Steering Committee Minutes/Memos, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 3/8)
  - Steering Committee Meeting Minutes/Notes, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 3/9)
  - Structure of Committees (Box-folder 3/10)
  - 'About Women's Studies at the University of Montana' guide, c. 2003 (Box-folder 4/1)
  - Annual Program Overviews, 1993-2003 (Box-folder 4/2)
  - Budget, 1999-2004 (Box-folder 4/3)
  - Clippings, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 4/4)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 4/5)
  - Correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 4/6)
  - Girlfriend's Guide for Women Faculty at the University of Montana, c. 2000 (Box-folder 4/7)
  - Program Development, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 4/8)
  - Newsletters, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 5/1)
  - Newsletters, 1998-2003 (Box-folder 5/2)
  - Newsletter Notes, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 5/3)
  - Newsletter Survey, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 5/4)
- Related Committees and Programs, 1971-2003; Series II; .8 linear feet
  - Academic Officer's Notes, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 6/1)
  - Ad-hoc Committee representing Full Time Faculty Women, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 6/2)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Faculty/Staff Meetings, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 6/3)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Chairs Meetings, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 6/4)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 6/5)
  - Council of Deans Meeting Minutes, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 6/6)
  - Gender Equity Committee, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 6/7)
  - Gender Equity Committee, Case, and Settlement, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 6/8)
  - Gender Equity Committee Salary Evaluation Kit (Box-folder 7/1)
  - Graduate Women's Studies Programs, 1995 (Box-folder 7/2)
  - Humanities Steering Committee, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 7/3)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings, 1974-1987 (Box-folder 7/4)
  - National Women's Centers, 1988-1997 (Box-folder 7/5)
  - National Women's Studies Association, c.1975 (Box-folder 7/6)
  - National Women's Studies Programs, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 7/7)
  - Provost Workshop, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 7/8)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 7/9)
  - Women's History Month Meetings Minutes/Correspondence, 2002 (Box-folder 7/10)
  - Women's Studies Minor at Montana State University, 1990 (Box-folder 7/11)
- Curriculum and Instruction, 1984-2003; Series III; 1.2 linear feet
  - Catalog Copy, 1998-2003 (Box-folder 8/1)
  - Course Lists, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Course Lists, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Course Lists, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Course Lists, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 8/5)
  - Course Lists, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 8/6)
  - Course Lists, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 8/7)
  - Course Lists, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Course List Review, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 8/9)
  - Course Lists, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Course Lists, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 8/11)
  - Course Lists, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 8/12)
  - Course Lists, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 8/13)
  - Course Lists, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 8/14)
  - Curriculum, 1991-2003 (Box-folder 8/15)
  - Department Enrollment Figures, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 8/16)
  - Department Enrollment Figures, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 8/17)
  - FIPSE Project/Women in Curriculum, 1984 (Box-folder 8/18)
  - Women in Curriculum, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Women in Curriculum, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 8/20)
  - Women in Curriculum, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Courses, Affiliate Campus Equivalents (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Syllabi, African American Studies, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Syllabi, Art, 1997 (Box-folder 9/3)
  - Syllabi, Biology, 1996 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Syllabi, Communication Studies, 1993-2002 (Box-folder 9/5)
  - Syllabi, Drama/Dance, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Syllabi, English, 1992-2002 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Syllabi, Foreign Languages and Literatures, 1993-2002 (Box-folder 9/8)
  - Syllabi, Geography, 1997 (Box-folder 9/9)
  - Syllabi, Health and Human Performance, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 9/10)
  - Syllabi, History, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Syllabi, Honors College, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 9/12)
  - Syllabi, Liberal Studies, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 9/13)
  - Syllabi, Management, 1996 (Box-folder 9/14)
  - Syllabi, Native American Studies, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 9/15)
  - Syllabi, Philosophy, 1994-2002 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Syllabi, Political Science, 1994-2002 (Box-folder 10/2)
  - Syllabi, Psychology, 1994 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Syllabi, Religious Studies, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Syllabi, Sociology, 1993-2001 (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Syllabi, Social Work, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Syllabi, Women's Studies, 1993-2003 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Masters of Social Work Program, 2002 (Box-folder 10/8)
  - Women in Science Project at the University of Montana, 1996 (Box-folder 10/9)
- Speakers and Events, 1971-2003; Series IV; 4.2 linear feet
  - Realities and Reaction: A Symposium on Women, 1971 (Box-folder 11/1)
  - Northwest Women's Studies Association Conference, 1982 (Box-folder 11/2)
  - Women in Curriculum Retreat, 1982 (Box-folder 11/3)
  - Regional Programs and Conferences, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Feminism in the '90s Conference, Spring 1988 (Box-folder 11/5)
  - Women's Studies Brown Bag Series, Early Years, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Speakers, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 11/7)
  - Feminist/Gender Studies Reading Group, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 11/8)
  - Co-Sponsor History, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 11/9)
  - Proposed Van de Wetering Lectures, 1993-2004 (Box-folder 11/10)
  - Women's History Month, 1993 (Box-folder 11/11)
  - Calendar of University of Montana Events Highlighting Women, Fall 1993 (Box-folder 11/12)
  - Fatou Snow, Guest Lecturer, Fall 1993 (Box-folder 11/13)
  - Brown Bag Series, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 11/14)
  - Brown Bag Procedures, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 11/15)
  - Women's Studies Speakers, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 11/16)
  - Brown Bag Series, Spring 1994 (Box-folder 11/17)
  - Charlotte Kasl, Guest Lecturer, January 1994 (Box-folder 11/18)
  - Bella Abzug, Guest Lecturer, February 1994 (Box-folder 11/19)
  - "Courage to Write" radio show, February 1994 (Box-folder 11/20)
  - Amy Ling, Guest Lecturer, March 1994 (Box-folder 11/21)
  - Jackie White, Guest Lecturer, March 1994 (Box-folder 11/22)
  - Janet Braun-Reinitz, Guest Lecturer, March 1994 (Box-folder 11/23)
  - Sue Giller, Guest Lecturer, March 1994 (Box-folder 11/24)
  - Symposium on Women in the West, March 1994 (Box-folder 11/25)
  - Women's History Month, March 1994 (Box-folder 11/26)
  - Carroll Smith-Rosenberg, Guest Lecturer, April 1994 (Box-folder 12/1)
  - Smith-Rosenberg Reading File, April 1994 (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Panel on Native American Women, April 1994 (Box-folder 12/3)
  - Poverty in Montana Panel, April 1994 (Box-folder 12/4)
  - Middle Eastern/North African Cultural Festival, April-May 1994 (Box-folder 12/5)
  - Lois Gibbs, Guest Lecturer, May 1994 (Box-folder 12/6)
  - Mark Johnson, Guest Lecturer, May 1994 (Box-folder 12/7)
  - Brown Bag Series, Fall 1994 (Box-folder 12/8)
  - Reception for Women Faculty, September 1994 (Box-folder 12/9)
  - Carol Williams, Guest Lecturer, October 1994 (Box-folder 12/10)
  - Ousmane Sembere Film Festival, October-November 1994 (Box-folder 12/11)
  - Dawn-Marie Driscoll, Guest Lecturer, November 1994 (Box-folder 12/12)
  - Julie McKay, Guest Lecturer, November 1994 (Box-folder 12/13)
  - Potential Speakers, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 12/14)
  - Women as Leaders Academic Seminar, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 12/15)
  - Faculty Women's Studies Retreats, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 12/16)
  - Faculty Women's Retreat Reader, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 12/17)
  - Diane Nash, Guest Lecturer, February 1995 (Box-folder 12/18)
  - Marginalized Literature Conference, March 1995 (Box-folder 12/19)
  - Patricia Locke, Guest Lecturer, March 1995 (Box-folder 12/20)
  - Speaker's Bureau, March 1995 (Box-folder 13/1)
  - Speaker's Bureau Working File, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 13/2)
  - Women's History Month, March 1995 (Box-folder 13/3)
  - Women's History Month General File, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 13/4)
  - Gloria Steinem, Guest Lecturer, April 1995 (Box-folder 13/5)
  - Christina Hoff-Sommers Reading File, April 1995 (Box-folder 13/6)
  - Anette Kolodny, Guest Lecturer-Cancelled, April 1995 (Box-folder 13/7)
  - Year-end Reception, May 1995 (Box-folder 13/8)
  - Brown Bag Series, Spring 1995 (Box-folder 13/9)
  - Prospective Brown Bag Speakers, 1995-2002 (Box-folder 13/10)
  - Brown Bag Series, Fall 1995 (Box-folder 13/11)
  - Reception for New Women Faculty, September 1995 (Box-folder 13/12)
  - Marilyn Chin, Guest Lecturer, October 1995 (Box-folder 13/13)
  - Conference on Sexual Assault, October 1995 (Box-folder 13/14)
  - Noretta Koertge Reading File, November 1995 (Box-folder 13/15)
  - Sarah Weddington, Guest Lecturer, November 1995 (Box-folder 13/16)
  - Carol Gilligan, Guest Lecturer, December 1995 (Box-folder 13/17)
  - Mentorship Program, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 13/18)
  - Speakers, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 13/19)
  - University of Montana Lectures of Interest to Women, 1996 (Box-folder 13/20)
  - Brown Bag Series, 1996 (Box-folder 13/21)
  - Patricia Williams, Guest Lecturer, 1996 (Box-folder 14/1)
  - Patricia Williams Reading File, 1996 (Box-folder 14/2)
  - Alison Jaggar, Guest Lecturer, March 1996 (Box-folder 14/3)
  - Speaker's Bureau, March 1996 (Box-folder 14/4)
  - Women's History Month, March 1996 (Box-folder 14/5)
  - Agnes Varda, Guest Lecturer, April 1996 (Box-folder 14/6)
  - Marginalized Literature Conference, April 1996 (Box-folder 14/7)
  - Take Back the Night, April 1996 (Box-folder 14/8)
  - End of the Year Reception, May 1996 (Box-folder 14/9)
  - Out of the Shadows, May 1996 (Box-folder 14/10)
  - Brown Bag Series, Fall 1996 (Box-folder 14/11)
  - Reception for Women Faculty, September 1996 (Box-folder 14/12)
  - Reception for New Women Faculty, September 1996 (Box-folder 14/13)
  - United Nations Teleconference, September 1996 (Box-folder 14/14)
  - World Conference on Women, Beijing, September 1996 (Box-folder 14/15)
  - Co-Funded Speakers, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 15/1)
  - Presidential Lecture Recommendations, 1997 (Box-folder 15/2)
  - Women's History Month Exhibit, 1997 (Box-folder 15/3)
  - Brown Bag Series, Spring 1997 (Box-folder 15/4)
  - Women's Studies Conference, February 1997 (Box-folder 15/5)
  - Carol Delaney, Guest Lecturer, March 1997 (Box-folder 15/6)
  - Carol Delaney Reading File, March 1997 (Box-folder 15/7)
  - Emily Martin Reading File, March 1997 (Box-folder 15/8)
  - Joan Brumberg, Guest Lecturer, March 1997 (Box-folder 15/9)
  - Speaker's Bureau, March 1997 (Box-folder 15/10)
  - Women's History Month, March 1997 (Box-folder 15/11)
  - Take Back the Night, April 1997 (Box-folder 15/12)
  - Brown Bag Series, Fall 1997 (Box-folder 15/13)
  - Cosponsored Lectures, Fall 1997 (Box-folder 15/14)
  - Chris Cuomo, Guest Lecturer, September 1997 (Box-folder 15/15)
  - Doris Schattshneider, September 1997 (Box-folder 15/16)
  - Reception for New Women Faculty, September 1997 (Box-folder 15/17)
  - Sheila Skemp, Guest Lecturer, September 1997 (Box-folder 15/18)
  - Ed Robbins, Guest Lecturer, October 1997 (Box-folder 15/19)
  - Miguel Scherer, Guest Lecturer, October 1997 (Box-folder 15/20)
  - Viva El Salvador, November 1997 (Box-folder 15/21)
  - Reception for Women's Studies Majors, December 1997 (Box-folder 15/22)
  - University of Montana Lectures of Interest to Women, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 15/23)
  - Brown Bag Series, Spring 1998 (Box-folder 15/24)
  - Co-Funded Speakers, Spring 1998 (Box-folder 15/25)
  - Fatimah Rony, Guest Lecturer, Spring 1998 (Box-folder 15/26)
  - Joan Copjec, Guest Lecturer, Spring 1998 (Box-folder 15/27)
  - Sister Rosemary Meyer, Guest Lecturer, March 1998 (Box-folder 15/28)
  - Speaker's Bureau, March 1998 (Box-folder 16/1)
  - Val Plumwood, Guest Lecturer, March 1998 (Box-folder 16/2)
  - Women's History Month, March 1998 (Box-folder 16/3)
  - Year End Reception, May 1998 (Box-folder 16/4)
  - Brown Bag Series, Fall 1998 (Box-folder 16/5)
  - Cosponsored Events, Fall 1998 (Box-folder 16/6)
  - Take Back the Night, Fall 1998 (Box-folder 16/7)
  - 5 Rivers Film Festival, September 1998 (Box-folder 16/8)
  - Provost Extravaganza, September 1998 (Box-folder 16/9)
  - Reception for New Women Faculty, September 1998 (Box-folder 16/10)
  - Brackette Williams, Guest Lecturer, October 1998 (Box-folder 16/11)
  - Shohini Ghosh, Guest Lecturer, October 1998 (Box-folder 16/12)
  - Recommended Speakers, 1999 (Box-folder 16/13)
  - Brown Bag Series, Spring 1999 (Box-folder 16/14)
  - Brown Bag Speaker Vitae, Spring 1999 (Box-folder 16/15)
  - Co-Funded Lectures, Spring 1999 (Box-folder 16/16)
  - Drew Faust, Guest Lecturer, March 1999 (Box-folder 16/17)
  - Lillian Faderman, Guest Lecturer, March 1999 (Box-folder 16/18)
  - Speaker's Bureau, March 1999 (Box-folder 16/19)
  - Women's History Month, March 1999 (Box-folder 16/20)
  - Women's History Speeches, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 16/21)
  - Ana Maria Shue, Guest Lecturer, April 1999 (Box-folder 16/22)
  - Joan Acker/Sandy Morgan, Guest Lecturers, April 1999 (Box-folder 16/23)
  - Take Back the Night, April 1999 (Box-folder 16/24)
  - Year-end Reception, May 1999 (Box-folder 16/25)
  - Brown Bag Series, Fall 1999 (Box-folder 16/26)
  - Women's Health Series-Cancelled, Fall 1999 (Box-folder 16/27)
  - Reception for Students and Faculty, September 1999 (Box-folder 16/28)
  - Reception for Students and Faculty, December 1999 (Box-folder 16/29)
  - Co-Funded Events, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 17/1)
  - Speaker's Bureau, 2000 (Box-folder 17/2)
  - Brown Bag Series, Spring 2000 (Box-folder 17/3)
  - Take Back the Night, Spring 2000 (Box-folder 17/4)
  - Diane Sands, Guest Lecturer, March 2000 (Box-folder 17/5)
  - Faith Wilding, Guest Lecturer, March 2000 (Box-folder 17/6)
  - International Women's Day, March 2000 (Box-folder 17/7)
  - Women's History Month, March 2000 (Box-folder 17/8)
  - Women's History Month Clippings, March 2000 (Box-folder 17/9)
  - Women's West Conference, July 2000 (Box-folder 17/10)
  - Brown Bag Series, Fall 2000 (Box-folder 17/11)
  - Sondra O'Neale, Guest Lecturer, Fall 2000 (Box-folder 17/12)
  - New Faculty Reception, September 2000 (Box-folder 17/13)
  - Co-Funded Events, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 17/14)
  - FRAU, 2001 (Box-folder 17/15)
  - Brown Bag Series, Spring 2001 (Box-folder 17/16)
  - Kristin Hoganson, Guest Lecturer, March 2001 (Box-folder 17/17)
  - Montana Girls and Women in Sports Day, March 2001 (Box-folder 17/18)
  - Brown Bag Series, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 18/1)
  - Linda Gordon, Guest Lecturer, 2002 (Box-folder 18/2)
  - V-Day, 2002 (Box-folder 18/3)
  - Women's Studies Retreat, 2002 (Box-folder 18/4)
  - Women's History Month, March 2002 (Box-folder 18/5)
  - Focus on Algeria, April 2002 (Box-folder 18/6)
  - Service Learning in Women's Studies Conference, October 2002 (Box-folder 18/7)
  - Brown Bag Flyers, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 18/8)
  - Lectures, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 18/9)
  - Women's Studies Retreat, 2003 (Box-folder 18/10)
  - American Men's Studies Association Conference, April 2003 (Box-folder 18/11)
  - Binder/Scrapbook: Women's Studies Program Programming Events, 1991-2000 (Box-folder 19/1)
- Other Women's Organizations, 1991-2003; Series V; .8 linear feet
  - AAUD Mailing List (Box-folder 20/1)
  - American Business Women's Association (Box-folder 20/2)
  - Blue Mountain Clinic (Box-folder 20/3)
  - Child and Family Resource Council (Box-folder 20/4)
  - Children's Defense Fund (Box-folder 20/5)
  - Clark Fork Coalition (Box-folder 20/6)
  - Community Resource (Box-folder 20/7)
  - Council on International Educational Exchange (Box-folder 20/8)
  - Feminists for Animal Rights (Box-folder 20/9)
  - Feminists for a Compassionate Society (Box-folder 20/10)
  - Feminist Majority Foundation (Box-folder 20/11)
  - Institute of Medicine and Humanities (Box-folder 20/12)
  - International Association for Women in Development (Box-folder 20/13)
  - International Center for Human Rights and Democratic Development (Box-folder 20/14)
  - International Programs (Box-folder 20/15)
  - International Sex Worker Foundation for Art, Culture, and Education (Box-folder 20/16)
  - International Woman of the Year-Tibet (Box-folder 20/17)
  - Missoula Biographies (Box-folder 20/18)
  - Missoula Family Violence Council (Box-folder 20/19)
  - Montana Shares (Box-folder 20/20)
  - Montana Women's Lobby (Box-folder 20/21)
  - NARAL (Box-folder 20/22)
  - National Women's Political Caucus (Box-folder 20/23)
  - National Programs (Box-folder 20/24)
  - National Women's Health Network (Box-folder 20/25)
  - NOW (Box-folder 20/26)
  - Outspoken (Box-folder 21/1)
  - Planned Parenthood (Box-folder 21/2)
  - Population Reference Bureau (Box-folder 21/3)
  - PRIDE (Box-folder 21/4)
  - Rocky Mountaineers (Box-folder 21/5)
  - subRosa (Box-folder 21/6)
  - Unitarian Universalist Women's Heritage Society (Box-folder 21/7)
  - United Nations (Box-folder 21/8)
  - Welfare Advocates of Missoula (Box-folder 21/9)
  - Western Montana Gay and Lesbian Community Center (Box-folder 21/10)
  - Women's Action for New Directions (Box-folder 21/11)
  - Women's Directory (Box-folder 21/12)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (Box-folder 21/13)
  - Women's International Network (Box-folder 21/14)
  - WORD (Box-folder 21/15)
  - Women's Place (Box-folder 21/16)
  - WEEL (Box-folder 21/17)
  - YWCA (Box-folder 21/18)